{
    "id": "b94443f3c0f44b09bf8c594d8798933f",
    "title": "Tenses Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "His father ....................... last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "die",
                "has died",
                "had died",
                "died"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "e28d5b47c7694b79b9636bcca523502a"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………….. Susie 3 weeks ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visited",
                "have visited",
                "had visited"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d002f504fc6b4351b34f040d47508e50"
        },
        {
            "question": "The sun ...................... when we went out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shone",
                "is shining",
                "was shining"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5c68e15f236e45a492d5df5192cdde45"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw him ..................... the lamp.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "steal",
                "stole",
                "to steal"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "22d25a678efd4dfc9310971c56ae5605"
        },
        {
            "question": "Yesterday I ………………….. a new cellphone because my old one …………………. stolen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "buy, is",
                "bought, has been",
                "bought, had been",
                "bought, was"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "18f9a93643dd4d34ad80d2d4a7809219"
        },
        {
            "question": "He thanked me for what I …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "have done",
                "had done"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1bb67a9cab944df9a79b591cb03b8ed9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... here for the last two years.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lived",
                "have been living",
                "am living"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fa3f4cb48607423ab50c378b295a4aea"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ………………… an apartment in New York two years ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bought",
                "have bought",
                "had bought"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9dea00c8f9624496ae073903bc1d7cda"
        },
        {
            "question": "I usually ....................... the newspaper in the morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "read",
                "am reading",
                "will read"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e589be2d5dbf4de8a97d6e6798c6174c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Ever since I ..................... my home state in 1995, I …………………. living here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave, am",
                "left, am",
                "left, have been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "71247eae6b7242d4a384feb44f3c8e7f"
        }
    ]
}